# Priyesh Tungare

+65 - 9277 4584 priyeshtungare31@gmail.com Blk 138, Bedok North St 2, Singapore 460138



#### **Profile**

Over 7 years of IT experience, spanning across Retail, Life-Sciences, Pharmaceutical, Logistics, SaaS and Telecom software domains. Highly adaptable in quickly changing technical environments with very strong organisational and analytical skills.

Involved in all phases of the Systems development life cycle including Project Estimations, Design, Development, Testing, Deployment, and Support and Maintenance for IBM Sterling Commerce (CPQ and OMS).

## Skills

IBM Sterling CPQ, IBM Sterling OMS, SDLC, JAVA, XML, Websphere Application Server, Weblogic, Requirements Gathering, Project Planning, Web Development

## Experienced In

- IBM Sterling CPQ Visual Modeler for Model Development, Customisations for Sterling Configurator, Rules Creation
- IBM Sterling Business Center Catalog Administration, Item Administration, Pricing Administration, Data Loading etc
- IBM Sterling Field Sales Quote Creation, Quote to Order Process, Pricing Adjustment etc
- IBM Sterling Order Management Participant Modelling, Process Modelling, Agent Architecture and implementation, Data Loading, UI Customisations, Inventory Management, DOM, Sourcing and Scheduling, Payment Processing etc
- Requirement Gathering and Analysis
- Implementing Software Development Life Cycle policies and procedures
- B2B implementation and Supply Chain Management processes.
- Project Management activities like Project Plan creation, delivery schedule, Project estimations etc
- Team Management

## Work Experience

#### SENIOR CONSULTANT - IBM STERLING COMMERCE, IBM SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE - MARCH 2012-PRESENT

- Responsible for creating Project Plan for model development and testing activities and ensure that the plan is followed as per schedule.
- Responsible for delivering new SaaS product models using Sterling CPQ 9.2. Involved in developing Configurator Framework, Configurator Rules to handle complex business logic.
- Involved in Creating Configurable Items, creating Pricing rules, PriceLists using SBC.

- Involved in end to end testing of the application using Sterling Field Sales and Passport Advantage.
- Involved in submitting Project Estimations for Sterling OMS project. Worked on POCs involving various modules of Sterling OMS such as UI Customisations, Agent Architecture, DOM, GIV etc

#### RELEASE MANAGER, ASTRAZENECA, MANCHESTER, UNITED KINGDOM - SEP 2011 TO MARCH 2012

- Release Planning and Co-Ordination for the Ariba OnDemand and Change Demand suites.
- Configuration of Change Management Tool.
- Release and Deployment Planning.
- Co-Ordination with different stakeholders to understand the schedule and plan the releases.

#### CONSULTANT - IBM STERLING CPQ, SAGE UK LTD, NEWCASTLE UPON TYNE, UNITED KINGDOM - SEP 2010 - APRIL 2011

- Requirement Gathering and Analysis of new enhancements.
- High Level and Detailed Design in Sterling MCS.
- Building the models using Visual Modeler and working on the Sterling Configurator.
- Working on Catalog Administration, Pricing Administration, Item Administration.
- Unit and Integration Testing
- Review, Testing and Deployment of developed artefacts.

## MODULE LEAD - STERLING MCS, INFOSYS TECHNOLOGIES LTD, MANGALORE, INDIA – JULY 2007 TO SEP 2010

Was involved in various projects during my employment with Infosys. The responsibilities and work profile was as follows:

- Requirement Gathering and Analysis of new business requirements, enhancements etc.
- High Level and Detailed Design in Sterling MCS.
- Working on Sterling MCS (currently known as IBM Sterling CPQ) Sterling Visual Modeler, Catalog Management, Pricing Management, Item Management, Customisations etc.

## Education

Smt C.H.M College, Mumbai University (Affiliated) - Bachelor of Computer Science - 2007

## Certifications

IBM Certified Deployment Professional - Sterling Configurator V9.1

## Declaration

I hereby declare that above information furnished is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date: 25th May 2015 Place: Singapore